buffet.com 2014-06-25

# This Privacy Policy is effective October 31, 2013, and governs Ovation Brands and its subsidiaries' and affiliates' (collectively, "we," "us," and "our") collection and use of information which you supply to us (collectively, "Information") on www.ovationbrands.com, www.firemountain.com, www.ryans.com, www.oldcountrybuffet.com, www.countrybuffet.com, www.hometownbuffet.com and other websites owned or operated by us or linked to this Privacy Policy(collectively, the "Web Site"). By visiting the Web Site, you consent to our collection and use of Information in accordance with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions or concerns about our use of Information or this Privacy Policy, please write to Ovation Brands, 405 Lancaster Ave. Greer, SC 29650.

This Privacy Policy is effective October 31, 2013, and governs Ovation Brands and its
subsidiaries' and affiliates' (collectively, "we," "us," and "our") collection and use of information
which you supply to us (collectively, "Information") on www.ovationbrands.com,
www.firemountain.com, www.ryans.com, www.oldcountrybuffet.com, www.countrybuffet.com,
www.hometownbuffet.com and other websites owned or operated by us or linked to this Privacy
Policy(collectively, the "Web Site"). By visiting the Web Site, you consent to our collection and
use of Information in accordance with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.
If you have any questions or concerns about our use of Information or this Privacy Policy, please
write to Ovation Brands, 405 Lancaster Ave. Greer, SC 29650.
Types of Information We Collect and How We Use It
From time to time, we collect various types of Information, including names, postal addresses, e-
mail addresses, domain names, telephone numbers, dates of birth, and financial information (e.g.,
credit card information in connection with your orders for products).
We collect such Information to monitor the performance of the Web Site, improve the design and
functionality of the Web Site, process and manage your requests for the purchase of products,
send you updates about our business and promotional information, and for certain other purposes
described below.
If you merely browse the Web Site, we generally only collect your domain name and keep a
record of the pages you visit to monitor the performance, and improve the design and
functionality, of the Web Site.
If you place an order for a product on the Web Site or visit a page that requests you to supply
your name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, and/or payment information (e.g.,
credit card number and billing address), we use such Information to process your order or to
otherwise fulfill the page-specific purpose shown, unless otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy.
If you supply us with your postal address, you will only receive the information or products for
which you provided your postal address.
If you supply us with your e-mail address in connection with any of our various clubs or programs,
we may send you e-mails regarding such clubs and programs, our business, and/or business
promotions. If you supply us with your e-mail address but do not want us to send you e-mails,
please let us know by writing to us at the above address.
We may also use Information to comply with applicable orders, laws, and regulations, enforce our
corporate policies, protect against misuse or authorized used of Information, and protect our or
others' rights, property, or safety.
Customers may request that Information not be used for purposes other than those for which it
was originally collected by writing to us at the above address.
Sharing of Information
Except as indicated below, we do not share Information with other organizations for commercial
purposes.
From time to time, we share Information with agents and contractors who provide us with support
for our internal operations. For example, if you place an order for a product on the Web Site, we

may share Information with a third party to process payment for, and otherwise fulfill, your order.
In addition, from time to time, we may share Information with governmental authorities who have
ordered or requested us to disclose Information.
In the event of a sale or transfer of some or all of our assets or business, we may disclose
Information to those involved in a transfer of some or all of our assets or business. If such an
event were to occur, we would strive to ensure that the recipient treat Information in accordance
with this Privacy Policy.
We do not partner, or have special relationships, with any ad server companies.
Cookies
“Cookies” are pieces of information that a web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for
record-keeping purposes. We use Cookies to make your use of the Web Site more convenient.
For example, we use Cookies to keep a record of products you add to your shopping cart.
If you do not wish to receive Cookies or if you would like your web browser to notify you when you
receive Cookies, please refer to the options menu in your web browser. If you disable all Cookies,
you may not be able to take advantage of all of the features of the Web Site.
Privacy Policy Updates
We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. In the event we modify this Privacy
Policy, we will post the modified Privacy Policy on the Web Site. We suggest that you check the
Web Site periodically to review our most up-to-date Privacy Policy. We will use Information in a
manner that is consistent with the Privacy Policy in effect at the time we collected such
Information.
Security
When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive Information such as financial information,
we redirect visitors to a secure server. Please consult the user documentation supplied by the
supplier of your web browsing software to determine how your software indicates whether a
secure server connection is in place. It is your obligation to confirm whether such a secure
connection is being used when an order is placed. We maintain security measures in place in our
physical facilities, or those of our vendors, intended to protect against the loss, misuse or
alteration of Information.
General Terms of Use
Please review our General Terms of Use that explain other terms governing the use of the Web
Site.
Other Questions or Concerns?
Upon written request to the address shown above, we will confirm the types and accuracy of
Information currently maintained about you; provided, however, we will not be able to reveal
Information we collected and subsequently discarded or destroyed. If you discover any
inaccuracies in such Information and ask us to correct such inaccuracies, we will do so.
If you feel that the Web Site is not following this Privacy Policy, you may contact us at the above
address or phone number.
